we're going to
modify our name.rb file again
this time we want to collect both the
user's first name
and last name separately
then we'll display a greeting to the
user that displays their full name
so in the first message that we display
to the user we want to specifically ask
for their first name
and we should also rename our name
variable
to reflect that it stores specifically
the first name
and if we just run our code as it is now
we'll input the first name bob
and our program greets us hello bob
the next step here is to collect the
user's last name
so we'll prompt the users specifically
for their last name
and we'll collect that user input and
store it in a local variable last name
in the same way that we collected and
stored the user's first name
so the last step here is to greet the
user
and display their full name
we can use string concatenation
but we need to be sure to concatenate a
space between the first name and last
name
so let's run our code
we'll input bob as the first name
now we're prompted for the last name
and we see our greeting with our full
name
we also could have written our code on
line five with string interpolation we
would wrap our variables first name and
last name
in curly braces this code looks a little
bit different but the output will be the
same
and we can run our program one more time
to see that
you